#### Contact

1025 S Central Pkwy Mountain House California 209 627 7732 (Mobile) veyyakulashabd@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shabdveyyakula-3b879a195 (LinkedIn) shabdveyyakula.com (Personal)

### Top Skills

Web Development Flutter HTML5

### Honors-Awards

Teen Tech SanFrancisco (1st Place)
Atoms and Bits (Second Place)
Global Youth Summit
SRC Hacks(Best App)
LA Hacks (Honorable Mention)

# Shabd Veyyakula

Coding Intern for PilotCity at PilotCity Tracy, California

## Summary

I am a 15-year old student attending Mountain House High School. I enjoy developing projects in my free time and I aspire of being an Entrepreneur. I enjoy learning new things that have allowed me to create amazing projects in the past. I hope to create even more amazing projects in the future!

## Experience

PilotCity

1 month

Digital Equity Fellow With Pilot City and Congresswoman Barbara Lee June 2020 - Present (1 month)

San Leandro, California, United States

A cyber-physical internship, fellowship, and entrepreneurship program for high school and college students to prototype, pilot, and productize solutions.

Coding Intern for PilotCity
June 2020 - Present (1 month)

San Leandro, California, United States

Learning and Developing frontend, backend and data analysis projects for the PilotCity platform

Xeon Developers
Xeon Developers
October 2019 - May 2020 (8 months)

Tracy, California, United States

## Education

Mountain House High School currently attending high school, Computer Science · (2018 - 2022)

San Joaquin Delta College English/History · (2018 - 2022)